Guide to the Peter H.L. and Edith Chang Papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series VII: Printed Materials
  - Subseries VII.1: Publications
    - On Mei Ling Soong Chiang
      - Lian He Weekly: Mei-ling Soong Chiang’s visit to an orphanage, Taipei 10 Dec. 1966 1 page (Box 31, Folder 04.06)
      - Unknown Newspaper: Mei-ling Soong Chiang at graduation ceremony of emergency service training class, women’s Alliance. Taipei [n.d.] 1 page (Box 31, Folder 04.06)
      - Unknown Newspaper: Mei-ling Soong Chiang’s painting as present to Sister Li Li Ya, Taipei [n.d.] 1 page (Box 31, Folder 04.06)
      - [LIFE]: Mei-ling Soong Chiang’s painting, Taipei [13 Oct. 1952] 4 p.. Reprint (from Life Magazine), (Note: Given by Mei-ling Soong Chiang to H. L. Chang ) (Box 31, Folder 04.07)
      - Unknown Newspaper: Mei-ling Soong Chiang’s speech on Communists, [n.p., n.d.]2 page (Box 31, Folder 04.08)
      - Unknown Newspaper: Mei-ling Soong Chiang’s Speech on the Presidents Beliefs, [n.p., n.d.]1 page (Box 31, Folder 04.08)
      - China Post: President and Mei-ling Soong Chiang Visit Factories of the Combined Service Forces, Taipei [3 September, 1970, page 5] 1 page (Box 31, Folder 04.08)
      - Unknown Newspaper: Mei-ling Soong Chiang Refutes Theodore White’s Allegations, [n.p.] 8 December, 1978 1 page (photocopy) (Box 31, Folder 04.08)
    - On William Henry Donald's Death
      - One album of news clippings in Chinese binding On William Donald’s death, [n.p.] 9-12 November 194625 page (Box 31, Folder 05.01)
    - On Chou ChingWen
      - Newsdom: On Chou Ching-wen, Hong Kong, 21 Sept. 1957, (2 pages ) (Box 31, Folder 06.01)
      - Newsdom: On Chou Ching-wen, Hong Kong, 12 Oct. 1957, (2 pages ) (Box 31, Folder 06.01)
      - Newsdom: On Chou Ching-wen, Hong Kong 9 Aug. 1958, (24 pages ) (Box 31, Folder 06.01)
      - Unknown Newspapers Chou Ching-wen and Peter H. L. Chang, Taipei [n.d.], (1 page ) (Box 31, Folder 06.01)
    - On Publications of Chan Hui Lu
      - Min Tsu Evening News: On Chang’s Chan Hui Lu, Taipei, 7 July 1964 1 item (Box 31, Folder 07)
      - The Kung Sheung Daily News: On Chang’s Chan Hui Lu, Taipei, 8 Jul. 19641 item (Box 31, Folder 07)
      - Min Tsu Evening News: On Chang’s Chan Hui Lu, Taipei, 10 Jul. 1964, (1 item ) (Box 31, Folder 07)
      - Central Daily: On Chang’s Chan Hui Lu, Taipei, 10 Jul. 19641 item (Box 31, Folder 07)
    - On Chang's Life
      - Collection of news about Chang, Peter H. L. [Taipei] 1964- Oct.1992, (2 albums- one of 53 pages with 36 pages attached, and one of 11 pages with 12 pages attached and one pamphlet inserted describing Former Residence Museum of H. L. Chang in Shenyang City, Liaoning Province, the People’s Republic of China with two entry tickets respectively. ) (Box 31, Folder 08)
    - Chang's Obituary
      - Sobelman list of Obituaries from "World Journal" and "Ming Bao" on October 16, 2001, New York: October 16, 2001, (1 page ) (Box 31, Folder 09)
        [H. L. Chang died on 14 October 2001]
      - Honolulu Star Bulletin: Chang, Peter H. L. Obituary, Honolulu: October 16, 2001 1 page and I photocopy. (Box 31, Folder 09)
      - Honolulu Advertiser: Chang, Peter H. L. Obituary, Honolulu: October 16, 2001 1 page and 1 photocopy (Box 31, Folder 09)
      - New York Times: Chang, Peter H. L. Obituary, New York: [n.d] October, 2001 2 pages (Box 31, Folder 09)
      - The Guardian (London): Chang, Peter H. L. Obituary, London: October 18, 2001 1 page and 1 photocopy (Box 31, Folder 09)
      - Himalaya Foundation: Notice of Chang, Peter H. L. documentary on occasion of his death. Taipei; October 18, 20012 page fax (Box 31, Folder 09)
      - Ming Bao: Chang, Peter H. L. Obituary, Hong kong: October 16, 2001 4 pages (Box 31, Folder 09)
      - World Journal (shi Jieh Ribao): Chang, Peter H. L. Obituary, Taipei: October 16, 2001 4 pages (Box 31, Folder 09)
      - Unknown Newspapers (probably World Journal): Chang, Peter H. L. Obituaries and chronology, [n.p.] Probably Taipei [n.d.] probably October 16, 2001 5 pages (Box 31, Folder 09)
    - Books Inscribed to Chang
      - Books inscribed to Chang (Box 95-96)
    - Subseries VII.2: Chronological News Clippings
      - Chang’s Life and Times, [v.p] 1946-1999, (32 Folders ) (Box 32)
      - World Journal, [n.p.] August7, 1926 1 page (photocopy) (Box 32, Folder 01)
      - World Journal, [n.p.] August 11, 1926 1 page photocopy (Box 32, Folder 01)
      - United Pictorial, Shanghai(?) June 16, 1946, Nos.177-178 16 printed pages plus 4 page inserted of which only one is dated –April 4, 1935. (Box 32, Folder 02.01)
      - One bound album of 21 pages of clippings 1947-1949 (Box 32, Folder 3.01)
        [Plus two inserted clippings]
      - Shen Bao, Shanghai: April 12,1948, (2 p. ) (Box 32, Folder 04)
      - Cosmos Newspaper (Xinwen Tianti), [n.p.] May 12, 1956, (2 pages ) (Box 32, Folder 05)
      - One notebook on Confucianism, [n.p.] 1956-57 [n.d.], (22 inserted printed pages from newspapers, a book, and a magazine ) (Box 32, Folder 06.01)
      - Taiwan Daily[?], Taipei 1960 [v.d.], (63 clippings of articles ) (Box 32, Folder 07.01)
      - Palo Alto Times, Palo Alto, CA: June 14, 1962, (1 p. ) (Box 32, Folder 08.01)
        [Article about Mrs.. John Bruce Dodd]
      - Gong Shang Rih Bao, Hong Kong: October 19, 1962, (1 p. ) (Box 32, Folder 08.01)
      - Unknown Newspapers, [n.p., n.d.], (4 p. ) (Box 32, Folder 08.01)
      - Unknown Newspapers, [n.p.] August 8, 1963, (1 p. ) (Box 32, Folder 08.01)
      - Gong Shang Rih Bao, Hong Kong: July 7, 1964, (4 page ) (Box 32, Folder 09)
      - Newsweek: Volume LXIV, No.5, New York: August 3, 1964, (60 p. ) (Box 32, Folder 09.01)
      - Unknown Newspapers, [n.p., n.d.], (5 pages ) (Box 32, Folder 10)
      - Unknown Newspaper, [n.p.] May 21 (?) 1964, (1 p. ) (Box 32, Folder 10)
      - Lian He Bao, Taipei: July 21, 1964, (4 page (2 copies ) ) (Box 32, Folder 10)
      - Xing Tao Rih Bao, Hong Kong: July 22, 1964, (4 pages ) (Box 32, Folder 10)
      - Gong Shang Rih Bao, Hong Kong: July 22,1964, (4 pages ) (Box 32, Folder 10)
      - Hong Kong Standard, Hong Kong: July 22, 1964, (4 p. ) (Box 32, Folder 10)
      - Pacific Stars and Stripes, Tokyo: July 24, 1964, (4 pages ) (Box 32, Folder 10)
      - Shenghuo yu Shichang, No. 12, Taipei: July 26, 1964, (4 pages ) (Box 32, Folder 10)
      - Tian Wen Dai, Hong Kong: July 26, 1964, (4 pages ) (Box 32, Folder 10)
      - Shenghuo Yu Shichang, No. 13, Taipei: August 2, 1964, (4 pages ) (Box 32, Folder 10)
      - Lian He Bao, Taipei: August 2, 1964, (4 pages ) (Box 32, Folder 10)
      - China Post, Taipei: August 3, 1964, (4 pages ) (Box 32, Folder 10)
      - Shenghuo Yu Shichang, No. 14, Taipei: August 9, 1964, (2 pages ) (Box 32, Folder 10)
      - Shenghuo Yu Shichang, No. 15, Taipei: August 16, 1964, (2 pages ) (Box 32, Folder 10)
      - Tian Qiao Zhoukan, Jiayi City: August 23, 1964, (4 pages (2 copies) ) (Box 32, Folder 10)
      - Jidai Piping: Volume 21: No. 10., Hong Kong: November 16, 1965, (28 pages ) (Box 32, Folder 11)
      - New York Times, New York: December 12, 1966, (1 page ) (Box 32, Folder 12)
      - South China Morning Post, Hong Kong: March 17, 1967, (2 pages ) (Box 32, Folder 13)
      - Unknown Newspaper, [n.p.] April7, 1967, (2 page photocopy ) (Box 32, Folder 13)
        [Note: Article on Zhou Enlai]
      - New York Times, New York: July 18, 1976, (2 pages both photocopies of same article. ) (Box 32, Folder 14)
      - Zili Wanbao, [n.p.] October 6, 1979, (1 page ) (Box 32, Folder 15.01)
      - China Times, Taipei; October 6, 1979, (1 page ) (Box 32, Folder 15.01)
      - Taiwan Xinsheng Bao, Taipei: October 6, 1979, (1 page ) (Box 32, Folder 15.01)
      - Lian He Bao, Taipei: October 6, 1979, (1 page (2 copies) ) (Box 32, Folder 15.01)
      - Unknown Newspaper, [n.p.] October 20, 1979, (1 page ) (Box 32, Folder 15.01)
      - Newsdom: No. 1653, Hong Kong: October 20 ,1979, (26 page ) (Box 32, Folder 15.01)
      - Da Cheng: No.72, Hong Kong: November 1, 1979, (80 pages ) (Box 32, Folder 15.01)
      - China Post: Visit to kinmen, Taipei: October 21, 1980, (1 page ) (Box 32, Folder 16.01)
      - Xingdao Ribao, [n.p.] October 21,1980, (1 page ) (Box 32, Folder 16.01)
      - Lian He Bao, Taipei: October 21, 1980, (1 page ) (Box 32, Folder 16.01)
      - Zhong Yang Ribao, Taipei: October 21, 1980, (1 page ) (Box 32, Folder 16.01)
      - China Times, Taipei: October 21, 1980, (1 page ) (Box 32, Folder 16.01)
      - Unknown author, [n. p.] [n.d.], (1 page handwritten notes ) (Box 32, Folder 16.01)
      - Kinmen Political Affairs Commission, Kinmen: 1980 [v.d.], (Two informational brochures of 6 and 13 page respectively on Kinmen. ) (Box 32, Folder 16.01)
      - Kinmen Defense Command, Kinmen: October 20, 1980., (1 page Itinerary Card ) (Box 32, Folder 16.01)
      - Lian He Bao, Taipei: April 5, 1983, (1 page ) (Box 32, Folder 17)
      - Unknown Newspaper, [n.p.] September 27, 1983, (1 page ) (Box 32, Folder 17)
      - LianHe Yuehkan: No. 38, Taipei: September, 1984, (pages 11-16, 19-22 and 107-110. 113-118 ) (Box 32, Folder 18)
      - Da Cheng; No. 136, Hong Kong: March 1, 1985, (pages75-76 ) (Box 32, Folder 19)
      - Unknown Publication, [n.p.] March 14, 1986, (1 page Photo Photocopy ( 2 copies) ) (Box 32, Folder 20)
      - ZhuanQi Wenxue: Volume 49: No.1, [n.p.] 1986, (pages 123-124 ) (Box 32, Folder 20)
      - Jinshan Zhongbao, Jinshan: April 3, 1987, (1 page ) (Box 32, Folder 21.01)
      - Unknown Magazine(Wang Yi Fang Xuejiu ?), [n. p.] May 6, 1987, (pages 64-66 ) (Box 32, Folder 21.01)
      - Unknown Newspaper (Wang Yi Fang Xuejiu?), [n.p.] May 6, 1987, (2 page (photocopies) ) (Box 32, Folder 21.01)
      - Unknown Newspaper, [n.p.] December 12, 1986, (2 page photocopies ) (Box 32, Folder 21.01)
      - China Women's Anti-Communist Liaison Committee To H. L. C, Taipei: October 20, 1987, (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 32, Folder 21.02)
      - Unknown Magazine, [n.p., n.d.], (1 page photocopy ) (Box 32, Folder 21.02)
      - Xianxiang Wenlu: Volume 3: no.2 (actual no. 10), [n.p.] March 20, 1987, (1 p cover photocopy ) (Box 32, Folder 21.02)
      - Ming Bao, Hong Kong: January 1, 1988, (4 pages ) (Box 32, Folder 22.01)
      - ZuiXin Xiaoxi, [n.p.] January 31, 1988, (pages79-90 ) (Box 32, Folder 22.01)
      - World journal (Sejie Rihbao), Taipei: March 24, 1988, (2 pages ) (Box 32, Folder 22.01)
      - Unknown Newspaper, [n.p.] 1988, (1 page ) (Box 32, Folder 22.01)
      - Doris (?) To Bob and Nora regarding article below., [n.p] April 13, 1988, (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 32, Folder 22.02)
      - Far Eastern Economic Review, Hong Kong; April 14, 1988, (pages 33-36 ) (Box 32, Folder 22.02)
      - Notebook, [n.p.] 1988 [v.d.], (4 handwritten p. and and 8 newspaper articles [v.d. 1988] and 1 page handwritten notes inserted. ) (Box 32, Folder 22.03)
      - China Post, Taipei: June 2, 1990, (1 page photocopy ) (Box 32, Folder 23.01)
      - China Times, Taipei: June 2, 1990, (1 page ) (Box 32, Folder 23.01)
      - Central Daily News, Taipei: June 2, 1990, (2 pages ) (Box 32, Folder 23.01)
      - Unknown Newspaper, [n.p.] June7, 1990, (1 page photocopy ) (Box 32, Folder 23.01)
      - Dongbei Wenlu: Volume 20, No. 4, [n.p] June 29, 1990, (Cover and inside cover pages ) (Box 32, Folder 23.01)
      - Unknown Newspaper, [n.p., n.d.], (1 page ) (Box 32, Folder 23.01)
      - Unknown Magazine, [n.p., n.d.], (pages 7-20 and75-76 ) (Box 32, Folder 23.01)
      - Times Weekly: No. 641, Taipei: June 10-16, 1990, (pages 45-46 and 51-54 ) (Box 32, Folder 23.02)
      - Liang Wang Zhoukan (international Edition), [n.p.] June 11,1990, (1 page photocopy ) (Box 32, Folder 23.02)
      - Wen Huibao, Shanghai: September 19, 1990, (1 page and 1 page photocopy ) (Box 32, Folder 23.02)
      - Ren Min Rihbao and Da Gongbao, Beijing and [n.p.] September 19, 1990, (1 page each ) (Box 32, Folder 23.02)
      - China Times, Taipei: October 29, 1990, (2 pages ) (Box 32, Folder 23.02)
      - Lianhe bao, Taipei: December 10, 1990, (2 pages ) (Box 32, Folder 23.02)
      - Unknown Newspaper, [n.p.] December 15, 1990, (1 page ) (Box 32, Folder 23.02)
      - Unknown Newspaper, [n.p.] December 24, 1990, (1 page ) (Box 32, Folder 23.02)
      - Unknown Newspapers, [n.p.] [nd.1988], (4 separate items of 1 page each ) (Box 32, Folder 23.02)
      - New York Times, New York: February 20, 1991, (1 page photocopy ) (Box 32, Folder 24)
      - Unknown Newspaper, [n.p.] February 22, 1991, (1 page photocopy ) (Box 32, Folder 24)
      - International Herald Tribune, Paris; [n.d.] February, 1991, (1 page photocopy [2 copies] ) (Box 32, Folder 24)
      - China Post, Taipei: March 12, 1991, (1 page -2 copies ) (Box 32, Folder 24)
      - China Post, Taipei: June 27, 1991, (1 page ) (Box 32, Folder 24)
      - Central Daily News, Taipei: August 14, 1991, (1 page ) (Box 32, Folder 24)
      - Seattle Post Intelligencer, Seattle: [n.d] 1991, (1 page photocopy ) (Box 32, Folder 24)
      - Unknown Newspapers, [n.p., n.d.] 1991, (2 one-page articles with 2 copies of one ) (Box 32, Folder 24)
      - China Times, Taipei; September 3, 1993, (1 page plus one photocopy ) (Box 32, Folder 25.01)
      - Lianhe bao, Taipei; September 3, 1993, (1 page ) (Box 32, Folder 25.01)
      - World Journal, Taipei; December 16, 1993, (1 page ) (Box 32, Folder 25.01)
      - Minsheng Bao, [n.p., n.d.] 1993, (1 page photocopy ) (Box 32, Folder 25.01)
      - Honolulu Star-Bulletin, [n.p., n.d.] 1993, (1 page ) (Box 32, Folder 25.01)
      - Unknown Newspaper, [n.p.] December 16,1993, (1 page ) (Box 32, Folder 25.01)
      - Unknown Newspapers, [n.p., n.d.] 1993, (6 items [1 page each] ) (Box 32, Folder 25.01)
      - Newsdom: No. 2356, Hong Kong: August 1, 1993, (74 pages ) (Box 32, Folder 25.02)
      - Da Cheng: No. 241, Hong Kong: [n.d.] 1993, (pages 44-45 photocopies. ) (Box 32, Folder 25.03)
      - He Wanbao, Tianjin, China [n.d.] 1993, (1 page photocopy ) (Box 32, Folder 25.03)
      - Komi Chang To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] October 18, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 25.03)
        [1 page printed invitation to tea party with handwritten signed notes.]
      - Unknown Newspaper, [n.p., n.d.] 1994, (3 page ) (Box 32, Folder 26.01)
      - Unknown Newspaper, [n.p., n.d.] 1994, (1 page ) (Box 32, Folder 26.01)
      - Hawaii Chinese Community News: No. 10, Honolulu; January, 1994, (2 page ) (Box 32, Folder 26.02)
      - Hawaii Chinese Community News: No. 11, Honolulu: February, 1994, (2 page ) (Box 32, Folder 26.02)
      - Central Daily News, Taipei: February 18, 1994, (1 page photocopy ) (Box 32, Folder 26.02)
      - World Journal, Taipei: March 13, 1994, (1 page ) (Box 32, Folder 26.02)
      - Unknown Newspaper, [n.p.] June 9, 1994, (1 page ) (Box 32, Folder 26.02)
      - Xinmin Wanbao, Shanghai: December 12, 1994, (1 page photocopy ) (Box 32, Folder 26.02)
      - Unknown Newspapers, [n.p., n.d.], (2 items-1 page each ) (Box 32, Folder 26.02)
      - Da Gongbao, Hong Kong: January 9, 1995, (1 page photocopy ) (Box 32, Folder 27.01)
      - China Post, Taipei: March 20 ,1995, (1 page ) (Box 32, Folder 27.01)
      - Xingdao Rihbao, Hong Kong: June 6, 1995, (1 page photocopy ) (Box 32, Folder 27.01)
      - Koinonia: First Chinese Church of Christ Newsletter, Honolulu: June, 1995, (2 page ) (Box 32, Folder 27.01)
      - World Journal, Taipei: June 17, 1995, (1 page ) (Box 32, Folder 27.01)
      - Dalian Daily, Dalian, China: July7, 1995, (4 pages ) (Box 32, Folder 27.01)
      - World Journal, Taipei: December 13, 1995, (page A10 ) (Box 32, Folder 27.01)
      - Unknown Newspapers, [n.p., n.d.], (3 items-1 page each ) (Box 32, Folder 27.01)
      - Truth Monthly (Zhenli Bao), Richmond, British Columbia: February 1, 1996, (2 p. ) (Box 32, Folder 27.01)
      - Unknown Newspaper, [n.p] February 20, 1996, (1 page photocopy ) (Box 32, Folder 28.01)
      - People's Daily, Beijing; March 29, 1996, (1 page photocopy ) (Box 32, Folder 28.01)
      - Beijing Qingnian Bao, Beijing: July 15, 1996, (1 page ) (Box 32, Folder 28.01)
      - Aisheng Bao, El Cerrito, California: August 15, 1995, (4 page plus 1 page photocopy ) (Box 32, Folder 28.01)
      - Unknown Newspaper, [n.p.] October 22, 1996, (1 page photocopy ) (Box 32, Folder 28.01)
      - Xinmin Wanbao International, Alhambra, California: November 8, 1996, (1 page ) (Box 32, Folder 28.01)
      - Qiao Bao, New York: December 27, 1996, (2 page ) (Box 32, Folder 28.01)
      - Hewan Bao, Tianjin, China: December 28, 1996, (2 page ) (Box 32, Folder 28.01)
      - Lianhe Bao, Taipei: [n.d] 23,1996, (1 page photocopy ) (Box 32, Folder 28.01)
      - Zhongxin: Volume 35, No. 4. Cumulative Issue No. 408, Petaluma, California: April, 1996, (25 page ) (Box 32, Folder 28.02)
      - Books and Bytes, New York: Columbia University Libraries-April, 1992, (6 page ) (Box 32, Folder 28.02)
      - Overseas Campus: No. 15, Campus Evangelical Fellowship, Lomita, Ca: February, 1996, (48 page ) (Box 32, Folder 28.02)
      - The Good news of the Hawaii Chinese Association: No: 32, Honolulu: April 2, 1996, (4 printed page photocopies and 4 page photographs of photocopies ) (Box 32, Folder 28.03)
      - Winston Chen To Peter H. L. Chang, Honolulu: November 26, 1996, (2 page, autograph letter with photocopy on back of one of news article about H. L. Chang ) (Box 32, Folder 28.04)
      - Unknown Newspapers, [n.p., n.d.] 1996, (2 items-one a photocopy ) (Box 32, Folder 28.04)
      - World Journal, Taipei: December 9-13, 1996, (5 articles [4 1-page; 1 2-page--one for each date] ) (Box 32, Folder 28.05)
      - Unknown Newspaper (probably World Journal), Taipei? -1996?, (1 page ) (Box 32, Folder 28.05)
      - World Journal, Taipei: December 29, 1996, (5 pages [4 articles] ) (Box 32, Folder 28.06)
      - World Journal, Taipei: January 2, 1997, (2 page article ) (Box 32, Folder 28.07)
      - World Journal, Taipei: March 30, 1996, (1 page ) (Box 32, Folder 28.07)
      - World Journal, Taipei: June 4, 1996, (1 page ) (Box 32, Folder 28.08)
      - Xingdao Ribao, Hong Kong?: June7, 1996, (1 page ) (Box 32, Folder 28.08)
      - Qiao Bao, New York: December 12, 1996, (1 page ) (Box 32, Folder 28.08)
      - World Journal, Taipei: June 3, 1997, (1 page photocopy ) (Box 32, Folder 29.01)
      - World Journal, Taipei: September 5 and 22, 1997, (1 page each ) (Box 32, Folder 29.01)
      - World Journal, Taipei: November 8, 1997, (1 page ) (Box 32, Folder 29.01)
      - World Journal, Taipei: [v.d.] 1997, (7 articles [1 page each] ) (Box 32, Folder 29.01)
      - New York Times, New York: October 5, 1997, (2 page ) (Box 32, Folder 29.02)
      - Unknown Newspapers and Magazines, [n.p] [n.d] 1997, (5 page newspapers and 4 page magazine photocopies ) (Box 32, Folder 29.02)
      - World Journal, Taipei; April 29, 1998, (1 page ) (Box 32, Folder 30.01)
      - World Journal, Taipei: May 8, 1998, (1 page ) (Box 32, Folder 30.01)
      - World Journal, Taipei: June 2-3, 1998, (1 page each ) (Box 32, Folder 30.01)
      - World Journal?, Taipei? [v.d] 1998, (3 articles [1 page each] ) (Box 32, Folder 30.01)
      - 98th. Birthday Celebration, Taipei: May 31, 1998, (1 p printed schedule and I page handwritten list ) (Box 32, Folder 30.02)
      - Vital Living: Issue 5-First Chinese Church of Christ, Honolulu: February, 1999, (12 page ) (Box 32, Folder 31)
      - Jianfan Niuxue?, [n.p.] [ 9/28 [n.year], (1 page photocopy ) (Box 32, Folder 32.01)
      - Sejie Huakan(World Pictorial) No; 112, Taipei? [n.d.], (pages 5-8 ) (Box 32, Folder 32.01)
      - Unknown Newspapers, [n.p.] [v.d.], (32 articles-1 page each ) (Box 32, Folder 32.01)
      - Unknown Newspaper, [n.p., n.d.], (1 page ) (Box 37, Folder 01.02)
      - Unknown Newspaper, Taipei: February 21, 1969, (1 page ) (Box 34, Folder 02.03)
- Series VIII: Audio Visual
  - One Tape and one Videotape (Box 35, Folder 04)
  - Fourteen VHS Tapes: 10 deal with birthday celebrations; 1 with opening of Chang Room; 1 Chang's memorials; 1 Edith and Peter's recollections; 1 religious and other matters by Mr.. Wu (Box 39)
  - Three boxes of Ten, Ten and Seven Tapes Respectively and One Separate Master Tape (Box 40)
    [See: Contents list in Box 41, Folder 3]
  - List of musical works on tapes in Box 40, [n.p.]: March 7, 1995, (6 handwritten pages with two attached notes ) (Box 41, Folder 03)
- Series IX: Photographs
  - Photo Album, (18 page -36 photographs ) (Box 35, Folder 03)
  - Photo Album, [n.p.] July 1950-1958, (48 page of photos ) (Box 38, Folder 01)
  - Photos, [n.d.], (Three separate photos in individual covers and three loose photos in plastic cover ) (Box 38, Folder 02)
  - Envelope with 4 photos of Peter H. L. Chang and Edith Chang (Box 42)
  - Envelope with three mounted and one loose photo of Peter H. L. Chang and wife (Box 42)
  - Envelope with folder containing 7 photos of Peter H. L. Chang and wife (Box 42)
  - Photo Album with 20 pages of pictures of Peter and Edith Chang and others (Box 42)
  - Two photos of Edith Chang-one is black and white and possibly wedding picture (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - One black and white photo possibly at summer palace with backing (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Box containing Photo Album with 40 pages of photos of the Changs (Box 42)
  - One unidentified rolled up place photo (possibly Shenyang) with writing (Box 43)
  - One Box with Photo Album with 19 pages of pictures of traditional photos of family and one inserted picture of Peter H. L. Chang[?] as youth in military uniform (Box 43)
  - One large separate photo of Edith Chang (Box 43)
  - One Envelope with 8 Christmas Photos in small paper Photo album, Los Angeles: December 24, 1988 (Box 44)
  - One Envelope with 62 loose family photos, North, Hollywood, California: March 11, 1988 (Box 44)
  - One Envelope with seven Family Photos (Box 44)
  - One framed Photo with cover of Mr.. and Mrs.. Chun, [n. p.: April, 1966] (Box 44, Folder 1)
    [Chang addressed to H. L. Chang and Edith Chang]
  - One small photographic reproduction of Huang Shan, [n. p.: April, 1993] (Box 44, Folder 1)
    [landscape]
  - One small envelope with 6 photos at Columbia-3 at Butler Library. Rare Book and Manuscript Library, New York: October, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - One Envelope with 42 loose photos, [v.p.] including Dalien, Chima: May-November, 1995 (Box 44)
  - Five separate attached photos-three of the family and two of buildings in pre-1949 China., Shenyang [?], [ n. d.] (Box 44)
  - Two mounted photos of Peter H. L. Chang-one attached to the back of the other (Box 44)
  - Photo Album With 25 pages of Photos Commemorating L. Chang's 90th. Birthday (Box 45)
  - Photo Album with 53 pages of Photos and Calligraphy Celebrating Peter H. L. Chang's 90th. Birthday (Box 45)
  - Photo album with 54 pages of photos and calligraphy Celebrating Peter H. L. Chang's 90th. Birthday-almost all in China and some of historic interest (Box 45)
  - 1975 (Box 46)
  - 1970-1985 (Box 47)
  - 1975 (Box 48)
  - 1976 (Box 49)
  - 1997 (Box 50)
  - 1978-1979 (Box 51)
  - 1984-1985 (Box 52)
  - 1986 (Box 53)
  - 1980 (Box 54)
  - 1987 (Box 55)
  - 1983 (Box 56)
  - 1982 (Box 57)
  - 1981 (Box 58)
  - 1963-1969 (Box 59)
  - 1988 (Box 60)
  - 1989 (Box 61)
  - 1994 (Box 62)
  - 1991 (Box 63)
  - 1992-1993 (Box 64)
  - 1996-1998 (Box 65)
  - 1995 (Box 66)
  - 1994 (Box 67)
  - 1978-1979, 1982-1984, 1989 (Box 68)
  - At Northwest University and Hometown (Box 69)
  - 1992 (Box 70)
  - Albums (6): 1969-1970 (Box 71)
  - Albums (11): 1990s and undated (Box 72)
  - 1930s-1950s (Box 73)
  - Albums (8): 1971 (Box 74)
  - Albums (10): 1940s-1965 (Box 75)
  - Albums (6): 1940s-1965 (Box 76)
  - Albums (7): 1969-1970 (Box 77)
  - Albums (4): 1971-1972 (Box 78)
  - Albums (8): 1966-1967 (Box 79)
  - Albums (6): 1973-1974 (Box 80)
  - Albums (1): 1997 (Box 81)